okay let's talk about Tiffany now let me just first start by saying that Tiffany Haddish has
always been super duper kind to me like I will call Tiffany Haddish my friend you know I don't
want to take that away I think it's also important though to acknowledge when people are behaving in
a fashion that is bigger than just your friendship in terms of its impact I'm a very very strong
believer in like I'll call you in before I call you out particularly if you're like my peoples and so
I did I did I hit her I hit her up and I said you know I'm very disappointed I'm very disappointed
and I'm very disturbed by your choices I feel like I lost a friend today and her response simply just
wasn't enough it wasn't enough because what it said to me was
you